{
    "id": "bf4437322cdd47968e5f0d147741c726",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I talked to the man ………………… bag was stolen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "whom",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know ………………… he wants.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is an ill wind ……………….. blows nobody good.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "God helps those ………………… help themselves.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Please try to understand ……………… I mean.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The flowers ………………….. grow on the mountains are very beautiful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the only chapter in the book ………………… is worth reading.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "All …………….. you say is certainly true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………….. dies for a noble cause lives forever.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope the little ………………… I have done has been useful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}